

CONTACT

- (Y)
 - +639165990579
- 0
- Lapu-lapu City, Cebu
- \vee
- jamesdaniel288@gmail.com
- jdenovero.com

SKILLS

- Front-End & Back-End Development
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, and MySQL
- WordPress Development
- O Divi, Elementor, and Beaver Builder
- O jQuery, Ajax and Vue.js
- Logical Approach
- Creative Ability

EDUCATION

Ernesto Rondon High School

2010 - 2014

146 Rd 3, Project 6, Quezon City, Metro Manila

University of Cebu Lapu Lapu and Mandaue

2014 - 2018

A. C. Cortes Ave, Mandaue City, Cebu

JAMES DANIEL ENOVERO

Web Developer

ABOUT ME

I'm a web developer with over 6 years of experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP. I also have expertise in Vue.js for developing web and mobile applications. I'm continuously learning and adapting to the latest industry trends.

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer

Proweaver, Inc.

August 2018 - January 2023

Converting design layouts into website pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and WordPress, maintaining and improving existing websites, interpreting and implementing instructions from clients, collaborating with team members, and fixing any website issues or bugs.

Web Programmer

Proweaver, Inc.

January 2023 - October 2023

Developing web and mobile applications using Vue.js. Creating and improving office tools. Conducting code reviews and providing feedback to other developers to ensure code quality and maintainability.

Front-end Developer

WebFX

October 2023 - Present

Building custom WordPress websites with ACF Pro, creating and customizing plugins, and utilizing AI tools to enhance efficiency. Enhance existing websites with updates and new features.